# Eduardo Santilla Jr

San Pascual, Santo Domingo, Nueva Ecija, Philippines 3133



junsantilla@live.com

**L** +63 927 669 7997



in linkedin.com/in/junsantilla



https://github.com/iunsantilla

# Summary

I have been engaged in web development for more than 5 years, working on a variety of projects. Presently, I am working as a freelance software developer and also pursuing personal projects to enhance my front-end skills. Additionally, I am actively seeking a full-time position that will allow me to further upskill and contribute my expertise to a dynamic team.

## **Experience**



### Software Engineer (Freelance)

Victorious Korean Language Learning Center

Feb 2023 - Present (6 months)

Create school portal web app with Next.js and Firebase.

### Wordpress Developer (Freelance)

College of Home Economics, UP Diliman

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023 (4 months)

Create College of Home Economics website with WordPress and Elementor.

#### Web Developer

Lokal

Sep 2020 - Aug 2022 (2 years)

Developed responsive WordPress websites with Elementor page builder and Shopify websites using PageFly. Integrated various plugins for security, performance, and client needs. Ensured regular website maintenance and backups.



# Web Developer

Anderson Group BPO, Inc.

May 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Conducted client meetings to discuss website design and function. Developed responsive and crossbrowser compatible WordPress themes from scratch or using page builders like Divi and Elementor. Integrated a wide-range of WordPress plugins to enhance security, performance, and meet client requirements. Ensured regular maintenance and monitoring of live website performance, with a focus on creating regular backups.



# Junior Web Developer

Anderson Group BPO, Inc.

Sep 2017 - Apr 2019 (1 year 8 months)

# **Education**



Wesleyan University - Philippines

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft Excel 2013 - Microsoft

### **Skills**

HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • PHP • React.js • Next.js • GatsbyJS • Tailwind CSS • Bootstrap (Framework) • WordPress • Shopify • Firebase • MongoDB • Git

#### **Awards**



Web Developer of the Year - Wesleyan University - Philippines Apr 2013

1st Place - Web Development Competition - Wesleyan University - Philippines Dec 2012